Thank you, good morning!
You may be seated, thank you!
Hallelujah!
Glory be to God.
I'm here to give you just a short word of exhortation.
You know God is working out the answer.
You remember the message given to you concerning reporting which is very important and I know
you are doing what the word says.
It's an issue that will really help you in your domestic affairs, your company and everywhere
You find yourself. The Bible says salvation is
of confession and believing
so you must know that
reporting should be an expression of believing.
Reporting should be what?
Should be an expression of believing.
Wherever you find yourself as a Christian, you are to report what you see.
As a Christian wherever you find yourself, you are to what?
You are to report what you what?
What you see and what you what?
Because when you report what you see and what you hear, it settles issues,
It answers questions,
It Clarifies doubts, and
provides a way forward.
Work alone
cannot help any establishment grow.
Every establishment
expects two things from you;
working and reporting
Today you are here in the church; you are to report whatever you see that is wrong among the workers and the members.
Don't just leave. If you say to someone at home 'no, no look at the way the woman behaved'.
You know when we were in the church, the woman was disturbing'.
Discussing this at home is a sin. You have to report it in church; you have to write it down
and give it to the OSHA to kindly submit it to the church authority.
You have to be vigilant. Be vigilant about what is going on around you.
Note the woman or man who is moving from one
group to another, moving around and talking.
Note the way he passes a note around the church!
You have to report all these behaviors
Hallelujah, that is very important.
Reporting should be an expression of believing.
You are to report unruly behaviors,
the visions you have about your establishments, dreams,
many dreams and visions you often have.
God will show you.
You can send a letter or a mail.
You can even travel from your country to another country just to report that vision you have because you are a believer.
Hallelujah!
I'm thanking you for your prayers because God has spoken regardless of our situations.
Hallelujah! so rise up for a prayer
If you honestly examine your heart in the light of God's word,
you will discover that there is a spirit of unforgiveness,
a spirit of anger, a spirit of bitterness, a spirit of jealousy, and a spirit of envy.
And such spirits, break our communion and relationship with God.
They open the door to whatever Situation you are in now.
You say 'I have sickness'. What is the root of the sickness? -Unforgiveness.
You say 'I have Hardship'. What is the root of your hardship? -
Envy, jealousy and anger. Those are the root causes.
The routes to get to you are;
Nightmare, barrenness, anger, jealousy, unforgiveness, bitterness-these are the routes.
Righteousness is the route to blessing and healing if you are honest to yourself and examine yourself in the light of God's Word.
Think about it. You will see many people you refused to forgive because of this or that, or because they cheated you ...
You will see people you have put in the prison yard and you are still working freely
everywhere.
You will see people that are in bondage just because of you.
Are you talking of divorce?
You have divorced many men and women and you said over your dead body will they see their children.
What is your problem?
Why will the man or woman not see their children? You people are already divorced
And you call God's name. For what?
You people are already divorced and you are still trying to keep the children away from your spouse.
Father forgives both the accused and the accuser,
forgives both the person who is wrong and the person who is right.
You say ‘this is witchcraft on you, they attack you’. who attack you?
It because you are caring unforgiving spirit;
Envy, jealousy.... and you say you are attacked. No one has attacked you.Once you have these spirits,
you have attacked yourself.
Are you there?
Listen to me again; they open the door to whatever
challenges you
are in. Are you sick, facing hardship
poverty,
loneliness, rejection? whatever you are facing,
the roots of those things are;
unforgiveness
envy
jealousy
bitterness. These are the roots. You don't need the enemy to attack you once you have attacked yourself
Once your relationship with God breaks, what else again? you are accessible to Satan.
It is easy now for Satan to finally break the communion and your relationship with God.
Once your relationship with God breaks, you are on your own.
Unforgiveness, envy, jealousy, bitterness, strife, hatred, just name it
open the door to whatever you are in
When you leave here now, it is not too late. From your heart you can say ‘what this man said, I am ready for it’.
Once you say you are ready. Are you in concord with your heart that the job is done?
When you leave here, you can continue to reconcile either with text messages, phone calls, whatever way you can.
Just try to settle yourself.
I release you from the pain of the past.
I release you from that unforgiving spirit.
That bitterness, envy, and jealousy. Be releasing in the name of Jesus!
You know, you can be released, you know that, you know that, be released in the name of Jesus!
Be release in the name of Jesus!
Such spirits break
The communion, and
relationship with God. Once broken, you’re on your own.
You're on your own.
And once you are on you're on your own,
here come poverty,
affliction, hardship, rejection,
and nightmare.
With pure heart man knows that Jesus saves.
With a pure heart man knows that Jesus Saves, heals, blesses and delivers.
With a Pure heart!
You keep saying
'I am healed, I am delivered” but
you are about to lose the healing, deliverance,
with that unforgiving spirit, bitterness,
envy and jealousy in your heart.
You can receive deliverance but because of unforgiving spirit, you will lose it.
With that unforgiving spirit, envy, and jealousy in your heart, healing and deliverance cannot be permanent.
That cannot be permanent.
This is why our life is epileptic. it goes up and down.
Up and down!
And you keep asking yourself why your deliverance and healing are not permanent
It can be forever. You are here forever. You are blessed forever.
It is a past victory but because of unforgiving spirit, envy,
hatred and bitterness in you, that cannot be permanent.
As you're standing, begin to examine yourself. Ask yourself;
What is wrong? what is wrong ?what is wrong with me? what is the Next step now?
It's better not to receive than to receive and lose it.
Ask yourself; What is wrong with me?
Why is my life not constant?
I'm happy and blessed now and another time, I am not
Why?
Jesus is the same yesterday, today and for forever
His blessings are the same yesterday, today. and forever. His healing is the same yesterday, today, and forever. Why all these?
Why?
How can you labor,
Sweat, and suddenly you are back to square one again.
You are here today because you
See the strength of God from strength to strength. That is why you are here.
Irrespective of tribulation, persecution, and hatred-
Strength to strength. That is why you are here
Irrespective of name-calling-
Strength to strength
That is why you are here.
When you expect something to spoil and it's not spoiled, you join them.
When you expect something to destroy and it refuses to destroy, you join them.
When you expect something to disappear and it refuses to disappear, you join them.
That is why you are here today.
Honestly examine your hearts
Christianity lies in the heart. Tell your neighbor; Christianity lies in the heart.
Your appearance is a camouflage.
Your makeup, your hair, your beauty, your handsomeness are camouflage.
The real man is your heart.
This is why the Bible says faith is of man's heart.
The one that worship God is your heart not your body.
Listen again!
Honestly examine your heart in the light of God's Word without prejudice.
Honestly examine your heart and
you will find out that your heart is full of unforgiving spirit,
bitterness, envy and jealousy.
Forgive us as we do what? Is that not the promise?
Forgive us as we for give those who what?
Why unforgiving spirit, bitterness, envy, hatred, and jealousy?
You are what God says you are. Why comparing yourself to others?
Why measuring yourself to others? Why?
You say 'I am too fat, I need to be slim. Look at that one, he is very slim.
When you see a beautiful car in the car park, you say ‘I must get mine”
You do anything to get yours
Honestly examine your heart in the light of God’s word ; you will see that your heart is holding grudges, envy and jealousy.
Father, release your children in the name of Jesus! Every unclean spirit in your career.
Father, release your children in the name of Jesus! Every unclean spirit in your life.
Every unclean spirit –leave my people in the name of Jesus!
God has spoken, rejoice!
Rejoice!
I cover you with the blood of Jesus!
I seal you with the blood of Jesus!
Be covered with the blood of Jesus!
Begin a new life, a new beginning.
A new beginning!, A new beginning! A new beginning!
A new beginning is a new life, a new direction and a new way.
A new beginning! A new beginning! A new beginning!
A new beginning! A new beginning! A new beginning! In the name of Jesus!
Four days ago, someone asked me a question;
Sir, am I the real person God wants me to be?
I said “What do you mean by that?”
He said because he does not know how to go forward again.
He said he is a Christian.
I said ‘so you are a Christian then you are saying this? This is blasphemy.
This is blasphemy.
If you want to be the person God
Wants you to be,
If you want to know your destiny,
then you need to know God better.
Get to know God better.
The way you know God now is by senses,
By your eyes,
Yes, this is true.
This is true. This is this. This is that.
You know God by what you see, hear and touch.
He asked me what I meant by knowing God better.
I told him; "you know God by your senses and if you think you know God beyond your senses,
I'm here now. What are you looking at?
He said 'I see your body, hands, nose,...' and I said 'No, no, no, no,
Our appearance is a camouflage.
To know the person God wants you to be,
to know your destiny, you need to know God better. Tell your neighbor!
I can't hear you.
You know God no doubt, but you need to know God better. You say, you know God,
you know God, but just by senses, what you see, what you hear and touch.
You cannot see beyond that.
Beyond this carrot, and TB Joshua you cannot see. All you see is the appearance.
You need to know God better
by discovering your spiritual gifts.
By discovering your spiritual gifts.
Because the Bible says no one can say 'Jesus is lord,' except by the help of the Holy spirit.
And God is spirit so you have to warship him in spirit and in truth.
How can you worship God without the Holy Spirit,
without the Spirit of God?
How can you know your destiny without the Spirit of God?
No, one can say 'Jesus is Lord,'
except by the help of the Holy Spirit. Without your spiritual gift, you are zero.
Without your spiritually gift, you continue to warship God by senses; what you see, hear and feel.
You cannot become God’s person on the history and theory about the word of God.
Tell your neighbor!
This is what makes you a child of God, a born again; History and theory about the word of God.
No, you cannot become God’s person on the history and theory about the word of God alone
The history and theory about the word of God are valuable but cannot work without the Holy Spirit
I command healing on you in the name of Jesus!
God has spoken! In the name of Jesus!
I can't hear you.
I can sense God's healing touching you.
I can sense God's deliverance touching you. In Jesus' name!
Hear this, God has spoken! Rejoice!
Don't forget the message for you.
The spirit of unforgiveness,
anger, and bitterness
break
the communion and relationship with God and
Once that relationship is broken. What else again? You are your own.
Those spirit; malice, bitterness,
Jealousy, hatred and unforgiveness.
If you have them in you, They open the door
to whatever
You are facing
and whatever situation you are in. Be it sicknesses, diseases, or whatever.
They Open the door.
You don't need the enemy to attack you. You attack yourself with these spirits.
You know what it means when Jesus says "forgive them as we forgive those who..." what?
With a pure heart,
man knows that Jesus heals, saves and delivers.
Please with pure heart!
This is why we give you bracelets
We have prayed over them, put them in the altar before giving you just to help you start growing like a
baby
Things of the Spirit, you have to start from the foundation
So you need to start it on the outside to reset your belief.
To reset your belief, to reset your believe!
Each time you sit down watching football on the television or whatever, It should be in your hand.
You should be saying 'Take more of me and give me more of you'.
you will not know when you shout out 'Jesus' instead of
'Hey'
Because 'hey' is more of your language.
So you have to be pregnant of Jesus to shout 'Jesus.'
We manifest what we possess.
We manifest what?
You manifest what you possess. Sometimes in the dream you see when
Your child, wife or husband sleeps side by side with you and suddenly he/she shouts; Honey, Honey!
And when you ask what happen, he or she says "it is a nightmare" because she is manifesting what she possesses.
She possesses 'Honey'
Even inside a vehicle when the vehicle is about to have an accident, you shout 'Hey'
You manifest what you possess.
So you have to possess who?
To manifest? Speak to me! Speak to me!
possess who? To manifest?
Meditating will help you; In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus .....
Even on the outside, you need something to help you too.
Meditate when you are alone and when you are about to sleep. It should be the last thing on your mind before falling asleep.
Just lie on the bed and continue saying "Jesus take more of me and give me more of you".
To flush out all the bad spirits in you.
You need that.
Let's pray for our nation.
Raise whatever you have with you as a contact point
Bless our nation, Lord. Redeem our nation, Lord.
God's intervention!
I can't hear you.
Yes, God's intervention! it's like every nation every country today faces challenges
I can't hear you
God's intervention !
Open your lips and begin to rebuke challenges,
corruption,
misjudge,
misrule, right now open your Lips and pray.
Misjudge, misrule,
Killing, stilling and destruction.
God's intervention,
in Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, pray for your leaders. Ask God to redeem your leaders and
Put them on track,
Strengthen them with wisdom and understanding,
Cover them with the blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ name, we pray! I can't hear you. I can't hear you.
I can't hear you. I can't hear you. I can't hear you.
Listen once again, God has spoken. You may be seated. Thank you
Hallelujah! hallelujah! Issue about your heart
Is a fundamental issue.
You have received all the deliverance and blessings here today.
All the deliverance,blessing and break through,
without a pure heart,
You will lose them
It is a pure heart that maintains the blessing of God.
It is a pure heart that maintains God's blessing.
So maintenance is very important. I know you have been delivered, but don't forget your heart.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus
Saves, heals and blesses
There's no way you can maintain God's blessings
without a pure heart.
So we have to be serious. The hearts I'm seeing are full of unforgiveness,
bitterness, envy, jealousy. I cannot continue preaching to you and yet you hearts are still full of those bad spirits;
jealousy, bitterness; hatred and unforgiving spirit.
I am still seeing lot of people seating here with unclean heart.
Yeah, many are seated down here. So this shows that
what is not permanent, is not of God, what isn't done well, isn't done at all.
So in this case,
Will you be ready
when the lord comes?
It could be tomorrow or when you are home.
Will the lord meet you?
Now I'm leaving you in faith, will I meet you tomorrow in faith or with unforgiving spirit?
I'm leaving you now in faith, will I meet you next Sunday with unforgiving spirit?
It's not possible
I'm leaving you now in faith, will I meet you next Sunday with bitterness in your heart?
Forget about miracle, deliverance, We are talking about your soul.
You talk about your knowledge in the scripture.
I know you have the knowledge, but only the history and the theory of the word of God
cannot save you .
Only the history and the theory of the word of God cannot save you .
You can preach the Bible from Genesis to Revelation,
quoting from verses to verses and yet on the last day, you still go to hell fire.
We are using the history and the theory of the word of God for the purpose of preaching and teaching.
This is the reason why we have the history and the theory of the word of God.
We are only made spiritual by living in the word and by the word living in us. That's all!
Tell your neighbor;
We are only made spiritual by living in the word and by the word living in us.
Your calling and your spiritual gift are one.
You talk about your calling. What about your spiritual gift?
When you talk about your calling, you are also talking about your spiritual gift and vice versa
So the whole thing is mixed up.
I want to leave you, thank you very much!